<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<eml:eml xmlns:eml="eml://ecoinformatics.org/eml-2.1.0"
	xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
	xsi:schemaLocation="eml://ecoinformatics.org/eml-2.1.0 http://nis.lternet.edu/schemas/eml/eml-2.1.0/eml.xsd"
	packageId="knb-lter-nin.6.1" system="knb" scope="system">
	<access authSystem="knb" order="allowFirst">
		<allow>
			<principal>uid=NIN,o=LTER,dc=ecoinformatics,dc=org</principal>
			<permission>all</permission>
		</allow>
		<allow>
			<principal>public</principal>
			<permission>read</permission>
		</allow>
	</access>
	<dataset>
	 <title>Meiobenthos abundance. Long-term variability and dynamics of estuarine meiobenthic
	 	populations for North Inlet Estuary, South Carolina, from 1972 to 1992, North Inlet LTER.</title>
		<creator>
			<individualName>
				<salutation>Dr.</salutation>
				<givenName>Bruce</givenName>
				<surName>Coull</surName>
			</individualName>
		</creator>
		<metadataProvider>
			<organizationName>LTER Network Office</organizationName>
			<address>
				<deliveryPoint>UNM Biology Department, MSC03-2020</deliveryPoint>
				<deliveryPoint>1 University of New Mexico</deliveryPoint>
				<city>Albuquerque</city>
				<administrativeArea>NM</administrativeArea>
				<postalCode>87131-0001</postalCode>
				<country>USA</country>
			</address>
			<phone phonetype="voice">505 277 2535</phone>
			<phone phonetype="fax">505 277 2541</phone>
			<electronicMailAddress>tech-support@lternet.edu</electronicMailAddress>
			<onlineUrl>http://www.lternet.edu</onlineUrl>
		</metadataProvider>
		<pubDate>2006</pubDate>
		<language>english</language>
		<abstract>
			<para>The original purpose of this research was to determine if natural
					meiobenthic assemblages exhibited continuity over time and to monitor several
					physical variables to determine if these influenced long-term temporal patterns.
					The most recent study focused on variation and the relations of meiobenthos
					abundance with environmental factors over 11 years. Typically marine benthic
					community studies are limited temporally and the majority of previously
					published 'longterm' meiofauna results (all taxa) were based on about a year's
					duration.</para> 
		</abstract>
		<keywordSet>
			<keyword keywordType="place">North Inlet Estuary</keyword>
			<keyword keywordType="place">Baruch Institute</keyword>
			<keyword keywordType="place">Georgetown, South Carolina</keyword>
		</keywordSet>	
		<keywordSet>
			<keyword keywordType="theme">meiobenthic assemblages</keyword>
			<keyword keywordType="theme">Zooplankton</keyword>
			<keyword keywordType="theme">ecosystems</keyword>
			<keywordThesaurus>LTER controlled vocabulary</keywordThesaurus>
		</keywordSet>
		<intellectualRights>
			<section>
				<title>LTER Network Data Access Requirements</title>
				<para> The access to all LTER data is subject to requirements set forth by this
					policy document to enable data providers to track usage, evaluate its impact in
					the community, and confirm users' acceptance of the terms of acceptable use.
					These requirements are standardized across the LTER Network to provide
					contractual exchange of data between Site Data Providers, Network Data
					Providers, and Data Users that can be encoded into electronic form and exchanged
					between computers. This will allow direct access to data via a common portal
					once these requirements have been fulfilled. The following information may be
					required directly or by proxy prior to the transference of any data object: <itemizedlist>
						<listitem>
							<para> Registration </para>
						</listitem>
						<listitem>
							<itemizedlist>
								<listitem>
									<para> Name </para>
								</listitem>
								<listitem>
									<para> Affiliation </para>
								</listitem>
								<listitem>
									<para> Email address </para>
								</listitem>
								<listitem>
									<para> Full Contact Info </para>
								</listitem>
							</itemizedlist>
						</listitem>
						<listitem>
							<para> Acceptance of the General Public Use Agreement or Restricted Data
								Use Agreement, as applicable </para>
						</listitem>
						<listitem>
							<para> A Statement of Intended Use that is compliant with the above
								agreements. Such statements may be made submitted explicitly or made
								implicitly via the data access portal interface.</para>
						</listitem>
					</itemizedlist>
				</para>
			</section>
			<section>
				<title>Conditions of Data Use</title>
				<para> The re-use of scientific data has the potential to greatly increase
					communication, collaboration and synthesis within and among disciplines, and
					thus is fostered, supported and encouraged. Permission to use this dataset is
					granted to the Data User free of charge subject to the following terms:
					<itemizedlist>
						<listitem>
							<para> Acceptable Use. Use of the dataset will be restricted to
								academic, research, educational, government, recreational, or other
								not-for-profit professional purposes. The Data User is permitted to
								produce and distribute derived works from this dataset provided that
								they are released under the same license terms as those accompanying
								this Data Set. Any other uses for the Data Set or its derived
								products will require explicit permission from the dataset owner.
							</para>
						</listitem>
						<listitem>
							<para> Redistribution. The data are provided for use by the Data User.
								The metadata and this license must accompany all copies made and be
								available to all users of this Data Set. The Data User will not
								redistribute the original Data Set beyond this collaboration sphere.
							</para>
						</listitem>
						<listitem>
							<para> Citation. It is considered a matter of professional ethics to
								acknowledge the work of other scientists. Thus, the Data User will
								properly cite the Data Set in any publications or in the metadata of
								any derived data products that were produced using the Data Set.
								Citation should take the following general form: Creator, Year of
								Data Publication, Title of Dataset, Publisher, Dataset identifier.
							</para>
						</listitem>
						<listitem>
							<para> Acknowledgement. The Data User should acknowledge any
								institutional support or specific funding awards referenced in the
								metadata accompanying this dataset in any publications where the
								Data Set contributed significantly to its content. Acknowledgements
								should identify the supporting party, the party that received the
								support, and any identifying information such as grant numbers.
							</para>
						</listitem>
						<listitem>
							<para> Notification. The Data User will notify the Data Set Contact when
								any derivative work or publication based on or derived from the Data
								Set is distributed. The Data User will provide the data contact with
								two reprints of any publications resulting from use of the Data Set
								and will provide copies, or on-line access to, any derived digital
								products. Notification will include an explanation of how the Data
								Set was used to produce the derived work. </para>
						</listitem>
						<listitem>
							<para> Collaboration. The Data Set has been released in the spirit of
								open scientific collaboration. Data Users are thus strongly
								encouraged to consider consultation, collaboration and/or
								co-authorship with the Data Set Creator. </para>
						</listitem>
					</itemizedlist> By accepting this Data Set, the Data User agrees to abide by the
					terms of this agreement. The Data Owner shall have the right to terminate this
					agreement immediately by written notice upon the Data User's breach of, or
					non-compliance with, any of its terms. The Data User may be held responsible for
					any misuse that is caused or encouraged by the Data User's failure to abide by
					the terms of this agreement. </para>
			</section>
			<section>
				<title>Disclaimer</title>
				<para> While substantial efforts are made to ensure the accuracy of data and
					documentation contained in this Data Set, complete accuracy of data and metadata
					cannot be guaranteed. All data and metadata are made available "as is". The Data
					User holds all parties involved in the production or distribution of the Data
					Set harmless for damages resulting from its use or interpretation. </para>
			</section>
		</intellectualRights>	
		<coverage>
			<geographicCoverage>
				<geographicDescription>North Inlet encompasses about 2,630 hectares of tidal marshes
					and wetlands near Georgetown, South Carolina, USA. North Inlet-Winyah Bay
					features high quality, ocean-dominated waters and salt marshes in North Inlet,
					contrasting with the brackish waters and marshes of Winyah Bay. The bay estuary
					is dominated by riverine discharges from a watershed impacted by agricultural,
					municipal and industrial development. Former rice fields and canals provide
					another system for study within the Reserve. The Debidue site is located at the
					confluence of Town Creek and Debidue Creek. The Bread and Butter site is located
					along the western shoreline of Town Creek adjacent to the mouth of Clambank
					Creek. The study site is the North Inlet marsh, a 3000 hectare high salinity
					estuary dominated by Spartina alterniflora, located approximately 6 km east of
					Georgetown, South Carolina. The marsh is bordered on the east by two barrier
					islands; on the south by a larger brackish estuary, Winyah Bay; and on the west
					and north by a mixed oak-pine forested peninsula. Debidue Site (DD) - Debidue is
					a sand-bottomed site located approximately .5 km inside the Inlet mouth adjacent
					to the confluence of two major marsh creeks, Debidue and Town Creeks. The site
					is at the lower end of an extensive sand bar and is subject to strong current
					and wave action. Bread and Butter Site (BB) - This site is located on a muddy
					subtidal bank of Bread and Butter Creek, about 100 m inside the mouth of this
					medium sized creek. The creek is 1.5 km SW of the Debidue site in the center of
					the marsh. The creek is 10 m wide at low tide at the sample site and is
					sheltered from strong current and wave action. The creek is lined with mud banks
					and oyster bars and the sediment at the sampling site is fine, silty mud. 
				</geographicDescription>
				<boundingCoordinates>
					<westBoundingCoordinate>-79.2936</westBoundingCoordinate>
					<eastBoundingCoordinate>-79.1042</eastBoundingCoordinate>
					<northBoundingCoordinate>33.357</northBoundingCoordinate>
					<southBoundingCoordinate>33.2125</southBoundingCoordinate>
				</boundingCoordinates>
			</geographicCoverage>
			<temporalCoverage>
				<rangeOfDates>
					<beginDate>
						<calendarDate>1972-09-07</calendarDate>
					</beginDate>
					<endDate>
						<calendarDate>1992-12-21</calendarDate>
					</endDate>
				</rangeOfDates>
			</temporalCoverage>
		</coverage>				
		<maintenance>
			<description>
				<section>
					<title>Entry verification</title>
					<para>
						Verification was performed at the input step using a program
						which creates a hardcopy to compare against the original sheets.
					</para>
				</section>
				<section>
					<title>Data last update while at North Inlet</title>
					<para>
						December 12, 1992
					</para>
				</section>
				<section>
					<title>Data last archive date while at North Inlet</title>
					<para>
						December 12, 1992
					</para>
				</section>
				<section>
					<title>Last Modification at LTER NIN site</title>
					<para>
						Data files format was converted from delimited to comma
							separated. Data was revised for consistency, agreement with metadata.
							Date: November 2006	</para>
					</section>
				<section>
					<title>Last Modification at LTER Network Office</title>			
					<para>Individual data files (LTER.NIN.MEIO.1972.txt,LTER.NIN.MEIO.1973.txt,
							LTER.NIN.MEIO.1974.txt,LTER.NIN.MEIO.1975.txt,LTER.NIN.MEIO.1976.txt,
							LTER.NIN.MEIO.1977.txt, LTER.NIN.MEIO.1978.txt, LTER.NIN.MEIO.1979.txt,
							LTER.NIN.MEIO.1980.txt, LTER.NIN.MEIO.1981.txt, LTER.NIN.MEIO.1982.txt,
							LTER.NIN.MEIO.1983.txt, LTER.NIN.MEIO.1984.txt, LTER.NIN.MEIO.1985.txt,
							LTER.NIN.MEIO.1986.txt, LTER.NIN.MEIO.1987.txt, LTER.NIN.MEIO.1988.txt,
							LTER.NIN.MEIO.1989.txt, LTER.NIN.MEIO.1990.txt, LTER.NIN.MEIO.1991.txt,
							LTER.NIN.MEIO.1992.txt) were concatenated into a single file spanning the
							dates from 1972 to 1992. Original fixed column format was changed to comma
							separated value format. These changes occured in March 2012</para>					
				</section>
			</description>
		</maintenance>
		<contact>
			<positionName>Information Manager</positionName>
			<organizationName>LTER Network Office</organizationName>
			<address>
				<deliveryPoint>UNM Biology Department, MSC03-2020</deliveryPoint>
				<deliveryPoint>1 University of New Mexico</deliveryPoint>
				<city>Albuquerque</city>
				<administrativeArea>NM</administrativeArea>
				<postalCode>87131-0001</postalCode>
				<country>USA</country>
			</address>
			<phone phonetype="voice">505 277 2535</phone>
			<phone phonetype="fax">505 277 2541</phone>
			<electronicMailAddress>tech-support@lternet.edu</electronicMailAddress>
			<onlineUrl>http://www.lternet.edu</onlineUrl>
		</contact>
		<publisher>
			<organizationName>LTER Network Office</organizationName>
			<address>
				<deliveryPoint>UNM Biology Department, MSC03-2020</deliveryPoint>
				<deliveryPoint>1 University of New Mexico</deliveryPoint>
				<city>Albuquerque</city>
				<administrativeArea>NM</administrativeArea>
				<postalCode>87131-0001</postalCode>
				<country>USA</country>
			</address>
			<phone phonetype="voice">505 277 2535</phone>
			<phone phonetype="fax">505 277 2541</phone>
			<electronicMailAddress>tech-support@lternet.edu</electronicMailAddress>
			<onlineUrl>http://www.lternet.edu</onlineUrl>
		</publisher>	
		<pubPlace>Long Term Ecological Research Network Office</pubPlace>
		<dataTable id="meiobenthicAbundance">
			<entityName>meiobenthicAbundance-NIN-LTER-1972-1992</entityName>
			<entityDescription>Long-term variability and dynamics of estuarine meiobenthic populations 
				for North Inlet Estuary, South Carolina, from 1972 to 1992, North Inlet LTER</entityDescription>
			<physical>
				<objectName>LTER.NIN.MEIO.csv</objectName>
				<size unit="byte">73000</size>
				<dataFormat>
					<textFormat>
						<numHeaderLines>1</numHeaderLines>
						<recordDelimiter>\r\n</recordDelimiter>
						<physicalLineDelimiter>\r\n</physicalLineDelimiter>
						<attributeOrientation>column</attributeOrientation>
						<simpleDelimited>
							<fieldDelimiter>,</fieldDelimiter>
						</simpleDelimited>
					</textFormat>
				</dataFormat>
				<distribution>
					<online>
						<url function="download"
							>http://nis.lternet.edu/NIN/data/LTER.NIN.MEIO.csv</url>
					</online>
					<access authSystem="knb" order="allowFirst">
						<allow>
							<principal>uid=NIN,o=LTER,dc=ecoinformatics,dc=org</principal>
							<permission>all</permission>
						</allow>
						<allow>
							<principal>public</principal>
							<permission>read</permission>
						</allow>
					</access>
				</distribution>
			</physical>
			<coverage>
				<geographicCoverage>
					<geographicDescription>North Inlet encompasses about 2,630 hectares of tidal marshes
						and wetlands near Georgetown, South Carolina, USA. North Inlet-Winyah Bay
						features high quality, ocean-dominated waters and salt marshes in North Inlet,
						contrasting with the brackish waters and marshes of Winyah Bay. The bay estuary
						is dominated by riverine discharges from a watershed impacted by agricultural,
						municipal and industrial development. Former rice fields and canals provide
						another system for study within the Reserve. The Debidue site is located at the
						confluence of Town Creek and Debidue Creek. The Bread and Butter site is located
						along the western shoreline of Town Creek adjacent to the mouth of Clambank
						Creek. The study site is the North Inlet marsh, a 3000 hectare high salinity
						estuary dominated by Spartina alterniflora, located approximately 6 km east of
						Georgetown, South Carolina. The marsh is bordered on the east by two barrier
						islands; on the south by a larger brackish estuary, Winyah Bay; and on the west
						and north by a mixed oak-pine forested peninsula. Debidue Site (DD) - Debidue is
						a sand-bottomed site located approximately .5 km inside the Inlet mouth adjacent
						to the confluence of two major marsh creeks, Debidue and Town Creeks. The site
						is at the lower end of an extensive sand bar and is subject to strong current
						and wave action. Bread and Butter Site (BB) - This site is located on a muddy
						subtidal bank of Bread and Butter Creek, about 100 m inside the mouth of this
						medium sized creek. The creek is 1.5 km SW of the Debidue site in the center of
						the marsh. The creek is 10 m wide at low tide at the sample site and is
						sheltered from strong current and wave action. The creek is lined with mud banks
						and oyster bars and the sediment at the sampling site is fine, silty mud. 
					</geographicDescription>
					<boundingCoordinates>
						<westBoundingCoordinate>-79.2936</westBoundingCoordinate>
						<eastBoundingCoordinate>-79.1042</eastBoundingCoordinate>
						<northBoundingCoordinate>33.357</northBoundingCoordinate>
						<southBoundingCoordinate>33.2125</southBoundingCoordinate>
					</boundingCoordinates>
				</geographicCoverage>
				<temporalCoverage>
					<rangeOfDates>
						<beginDate>
							<calendarDate>1972-09-07</calendarDate>
						</beginDate>
						<endDate>
							<calendarDate>1992-12-21</calendarDate>
						</endDate>
					</rangeOfDates>
				</temporalCoverage>
			</coverage>
			<methods>
				<methodStep>
					<description>
						<section>
							<title>Research methods</title>
							<para> 
						    Each core sample was extruded and immediately fixed in 10
							percent borax-buffered formalin with Rose Bengal. Salinity was measured
							by refractometer and Eh (September 1972 - December 1976) by platinum
							electrode. Oxidizable organic matter was determined using the wet
							dichromate method (Walkley and Black 1934). Granulometric parameters
							were measured by wet sieving through phi series sieves to 63
							micrometers, and drying and weighing the sediment retained on the
							sieves. An aliquot of the material passing the 63 micrometer sieve was
							removed for pipette analysis (Folk 1968). Sorting coefficient was
							calculated using methods by Trask (1932). Mud samples were extracted
							using Ludox centrifugation (de Jonge and Bowmann 1977); the sand samples
							by the shaking-supernatant technique of Wieser (1960). All animals
							retained on a 63 micrometer sieve were enumerated to major taxon; every
							copepod and every 4th nematode was removed for species identification.
							Since all sorted samples were formalin fixed, soft-bodied taxa abundance
							(e.g. gastrotrichs, turbellarians, ciliates) was probably underestimated
							(Hulings and Gray 1971). Ciliates may have been further underestimated
							since the samples were collected on a 63 micrometer sieve; thus only the
							larger ciliates (e.g. Tracheloraphis spp.) were retained.
					  	</para>
							</section>
						<section>
						<title>Experimental Design</title>
						<para>The study sites (1 sand, 1 mud) in North Inlet, South
								Carolina, USA, were sampled monthly from January 1973 through
								December 1980 and every two weeks from January 1981 - December 1983.
								At each site 4 replicate core samples were taken up to March 1976, 3
								replicates from April 1976 - December 1980 and 2 replicates from
								January 1981 December 1983. All cores were taken to the depth of the
								redox potential discontinuity (RPD); typically 1 to 2 centimeters in
								mud; 4 to 10 centimeters in sand. Both sites are subtidal, located 1
								meter below MLW. Sediment samples were collected for organic
								analysis up to 1978, and for sediment size analysis monthly or
								quarterly (up to September 1979) and then monthly (March - December
								1983). Four data sets were collected to assess potential temperature
								effects: (1) surface-sediment temperature measurements taken at the
								time of meiofauna sample collection (January 1973 - December 1983);
								(2) minimum and maximum daily air temperature recorded at the
								Georgetown County, SC, Airport from January 1935 - December 1978 (44
								yr); (3) daily surface water temperatures from the mouth of the
								North Inlet estuary, June 1979 - December 1983; (4) heating and
								cooling degree days data collected at the Charleston Airport,
								Charleston, SC, December 1968 - April 1984. 
						</para>
							</section>
					</description>
				</methodStep>
			</methods>			
			<attributeList>
				<attribute id="meiobenthicAbundance.DATE">
					<attributeName>DATE</attributeName>
					<attributeLabel>DATE</attributeLabel>
					<attributeDefinition>Date when sample collected</attributeDefinition>
					<storageType 
						typeSystem="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-datatypes">date</storageType>
					<measurementScale>
						<dateTime>
							<formatString>YYYY-MM-DD</formatString>
						</dateTime>
					</measurementScale>
				</attribute>
				<attribute id="meiobenthicAbundance.SITE">
					<attributeName> SITE</attributeName>
					<attributeLabel>SITE</attributeLabel>
					<attributeDefinition> Site where sample was collected </attributeDefinition>
					<measurementScale>
						<nominal>
							<nonNumericDomain>
								<enumeratedDomain>
									<codeDefinition>
										<code>BB</code>
										<definition>Bread and Butter</definition>
									</codeDefinition>
									<codeDefinition>
										<code>DD</code>
										<definition>Debidue Site</definition>
									</codeDefinition>
								</enumeratedDomain>
							</nonNumericDomain>
						</nominal>
					</measurementScale>
				</attribute>
				<attribute id="meiobenthicAbundance.NEMA">
					<attributeName> Nematodes</attributeName>
					<attributeLabel>NEMA</attributeLabel>
					<attributeDefinition> density of nematodes, number per 10 square centimeter </attributeDefinition>
					<measurementScale>
						<interval>
							<unit>
								<customUnit>numberPer10CentimeterSquared</customUnit>
							</unit>
							<precision>1</precision>
							<numericDomain>
								<numberType>real</numberType>
								<bounds>
								<minimum exclusive="false">0 </minimum>
								<maximum exclusive="false">6300</maximum>
							    </bounds>
							</numericDomain>
							</interval>
					</measurementScale>
					<missingValueCode>
						<code>-99</code>
						<codeExplanation>missing value</codeExplanation>
					</missingValueCode>
				</attribute>
				<attribute id="meiobenthicAbundance.COPE">
					<attributeName> Copepods</attributeName>
					<attributeLabel>COPE</attributeLabel>
					<attributeDefinition> density of copepods, number per 10 square centimeter </attributeDefinition>
					<measurementScale>
						<interval>
							<unit>
								<customUnit>numberPer10CentimeterSquared</customUnit>
							</unit>
							<precision>1</precision>
							<numericDomain>
								<numberType>real</numberType>
								<bounds>
								<minimum exclusive="false">0 </minimum>
								<maximum exclusive="false">1100</maximum>
							</bounds>				
							</numericDomain>
						</interval>
					</measurementScale>
					<missingValueCode>
						<code>-99</code>
						<codeExplanation>missing value</codeExplanation>
					</missingValueCode>
				</attribute>
				<attribute id="meiobenthicAbundance.NAUP">
					<attributeName> Copepod nauplii</attributeName>
					<attributeLabel>NAUP</attributeLabel>
					<attributeDefinition> density of Copepod nauplii, number per 10 square centimeter</attributeDefinition>
					<measurementScale>
						<interval>
							<unit>
								<customUnit>numberPer10CentimeterSquared</customUnit>
							</unit>
							<precision>1</precision>							
							<numericDomain>
								<numberType>real</numberType>
								<bounds>
									<minimum exclusive="false">0 </minimum>
									<maximum exclusive="false">1500</maximum>
								</bounds>
							</numericDomain>
						</interval>
					</measurementScale>
					<missingValueCode>
						<code>-99</code>
						<codeExplanation>missing value</codeExplanation>
					</missingValueCode>
				</attribute>
				<attribute id="meiobenthicAbundance.OSTR">
					<attributeName> Ostracods</attributeName>
					<attributeLabel>OSTR</attributeLabel>
					<attributeDefinition> Density of Ostracods, number per 10 square centimeter</attributeDefinition>
					<measurementScale>
						<interval>
							<unit>
								<customUnit>numberPer10CentimeterSquared</customUnit>
							</unit>
							<precision>1</precision>
							<numericDomain>
								<numberType>real</numberType>
								<bounds>
									<minimum exclusive="false">0 </minimum>
									<maximum exclusive="false">400</maximum>
								</bounds>
							</numericDomain>
						</interval>
					</measurementScale>
					<missingValueCode>
						<code>-99</code>
						<codeExplanation>missing value</codeExplanation>
					</missingValueCode>
				</attribute>
				<attribute id="meiobenthicAbundance.GAST">
					<attributeName> Gastrotrichs</attributeName>
					<attributeLabel>GAST</attributeLabel>
					<attributeDefinition> Density of/ Gastrotrichs,number per 10 square centimeter</attributeDefinition>
					<measurementScale>
						<interval>
							<unit>
								<customUnit>numberPer10CentimeterSquared</customUnit>
							</unit>
							<precision>1</precision>
							<numericDomain>
								<numberType>real</numberType>
								<bounds>
									<minimum exclusive="false">0 </minimum>
									<maximum exclusive="false">1650</maximum>
								</bounds>
							</numericDomain>
						</interval>
					</measurementScale>
					<missingValueCode>
						<code>-99</code>
						<codeExplanation>missing value</codeExplanation>
					</missingValueCode>
				</attribute>
				<attribute id="meiobenthicAbundance.CILI">
					<attributeName> Ciliates</attributeName>
					<attributeLabel>CILI</attributeLabel>
					<attributeDefinition> Density of Ciliates,number per 10 square centimeter</attributeDefinition>
					<measurementScale>
						<interval>
							<unit>
								<customUnit>numberPer10CentimeterSquared</customUnit>
							</unit>
							<precision>1</precision>
							<numericDomain>
								<numberType>real</numberType>
								<bounds>
									<minimum exclusive="false">0 </minimum>
									<maximum exclusive="false">750</maximum>
								</bounds>
							</numericDomain>
						</interval>
					</measurementScale>
					<missingValueCode>
						<code>-99</code>
						<codeExplanation>missing value</codeExplanation>
					</missingValueCode>
				</attribute>
				<attribute id="meiobenthicAbundance.TURB">
					<attributeName> Turbelarians</attributeName>
					<attributeLabel>TURB</attributeLabel>
					<attributeDefinition> Density of Turbelarians,number per 10 square centimeter</attributeDefinition>
					<measurementScale>
						<interval>
							<unit>
								<customUnit>numberPer10CentimeterSquared</customUnit>
							</unit>
							<precision>1</precision>
							<numericDomain>
								<numberType>real</numberType>
								<bounds>
									<minimum exclusive="false">0 </minimum>
									<maximum exclusive="false">400</maximum>
								</bounds>
							</numericDomain>
						</interval>
					</measurementScale>
					<missingValueCode>
						<code>-99</code>
						<codeExplanation>missing value</codeExplanation>
					</missingValueCode>
				</attribute>
				<attribute id="meiobenthicAbundance.POLY">
					<attributeName> Polychaetes</attributeName>
					<attributeLabel>POLY</attributeLabel>
					<attributeDefinition> Density of Polychaetes,number per 10 square centimeter</attributeDefinition>
					<measurementScale>
						<interval>
							<unit>
								<customUnit>numberPer10CentimeterSquared</customUnit>
							</unit>
							<precision>1</precision>
							<numericDomain>
								<numberType>real</numberType>
								<bounds>
									<minimum exclusive="false">0 </minimum>
									<maximum exclusive="false">780</maximum>
								</bounds>
							</numericDomain>
						</interval>
					</measurementScale>
					<missingValueCode>
						<code>-99</code>
						<codeExplanation>missing value</codeExplanation>
					</missingValueCode>
				</attribute>
				<attribute id="meiobenthicAbundance.BIVA">
					<attributeName> Bivalves</attributeName>
					<attributeLabel>BIVA</attributeLabel>
					<attributeDefinition> Density of bivalves, number per 10 square centimeter</attributeDefinition>
					<measurementScale>
						<interval>
							<unit>
								<customUnit>numberPer10CentimeterSquared</customUnit>
							</unit>
							<precision>1</precision>
							<numericDomain>
								<numberType>real</numberType>
								<bounds>
									<minimum exclusive="false">0 </minimum>
									<maximum exclusive="false">300</maximum>
								</bounds>
							</numericDomain>
						</interval>
					</measurementScale>
					<missingValueCode>
						<code>-99</code>
						<codeExplanation>missing value</codeExplanation>
					</missingValueCode>
				</attribute>
			</attributeList>
			<numberOfRecords>1747</numberOfRecords>
		</dataTable>
	</dataset>
	<additionalMetadata>
		<metadata>
			<stmml:unitList xmlns:stmml="http://www.xml-cml.org/schema/stmml-1.1"
				xmlns:sch="http://www.ascc.net/xml/schematron"
				xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
				xmlns="http://www.xml-cml.org/schema/stmml"
				xsi:schemaLocation="http://www.xml-cml.org/schema/stmml-1.1 http://nis.lternet.edu/schemas/eml/eml-2.1.0/stmml.xsd">
				<stmml:unit id="numberPer10CentimeterSquared" name="numberPer10CentimeterSquared" 
				abbreviation="number/10cm2" unitType="arealDensity" parentSI="numberPerCentimeterSquared" 
				multiplierToSI="0.1" constantToSI="0">
					<stmml:description>number per 10 square centimeter</stmml:description>
				</stmml:unit>
				</stmml:unitList>
		</metadata>
		</additionalMetadata>
</eml:eml>




