<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<eml:eml xmlns:eml="eml://ecoinformatics.org/eml-2.1.0"
    xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
    xsi:schemaLocation="eml://ecoinformatics.org/eml-2.1.0 http://nis.lternet.edu/schemas/eml/eml-2.1.0/eml.xsd"
    packageId="knb-lter-nin.3.1" system="knb" scope="system">
    <access authSystem="knb" order="allowFirst">
        <allow>
            <principal>uid=NIN,o=LTER,dc=ecoinformatics,dc=org</principal>
            <permission>all</permission>
        </allow>
        <allow>
            <principal>public</principal>
            <permission>read</permission>
        </allow>
    </access>
    <dataset>
        <title>National Weather Service data for North Inlet Estuary, South Carolina, from 1986 to 1992, North Inlet LTER</title>
        <creator>
            <individualName>
                <salutation>Dr.</salutation>
                <givenName>William</givenName>
                <givenName>K.</givenName>
                <surName>Michener</surName>
            </individualName>
        </creator>
        <creator>
            <individualName>
                <givenName>Mr.</givenName>
                <givenName>Daniel</givenName>
                <surName>Taylor</surName>
            </individualName>
        </creator>
        <metadataProvider>
            <organizationName>LTER Network Office</organizationName>
            <address>
				<deliveryPoint>UNM Biology Department, MSC03-2020</deliveryPoint>
				<deliveryPoint>1 University of New Mexico</deliveryPoint>
				<city>Albuquerque</city>
				<administrativeArea>NM</administrativeArea>
				<postalCode>87131-0001</postalCode>
				<country>USA</country>
			</address>
            <phone phonetype="voice">505 277 2535</phone>
            <phone phonetype="fax">505 277 2541</phone>
            <electronicMailAddress>tech-support@lternet.edu</electronicMailAddress>
            <onlineUrl>http://www.lternet.edu</onlineUrl>
        </metadataProvider>
        <pubDate>2006</pubDate>
        <language>english</language>
        <abstract>
            <para>This data package consists of National Weather Service data for North Inlet Estuary, 
                South Carolina, from 1986 to 1992, North Inlet LTER. It's purpose is to
                To develop a long-term climate record for the North Inlet Estuary LTER site; 
                For short and long-term studies at North Inlet and for comparisons to
                other LTER and NWS sites. </para>
        </abstract>
        <keywordSet>
            <keyword keywordType="theme">Temperature</keyword>
            <keyword keywordType="theme">Precipitation</keyword>
            <keyword keywordType="place">North Inlet Estuarine</keyword>
            <keyword keywordType="place">Baruch Institute</keyword>
            <keyword keywordType="place">Georgetown, South Carolina</keyword>
        </keywordSet>
        <intellectualRights>
            <section>
                <title>LTER Network Data Access Requirements</title>
                <para> The access to all LTER data is subject to requirements set forth by this
                    policy document to enable data providers to track usage, evaluate its impact in
                    the community, and confirm users' acceptance of the terms of acceptable use.
                    These requirements are standardized across the LTER Network to provide
                    contractual exchange of data between Site Data Providers, Network Data
                    Providers, and Data Users that can be encoded into electronic form and exchanged
                    between computers. This will allow direct access to data via a common portal
                    once these requirements have been fulfilled. The following information may be
                    required directly or by proxy prior to the transference of any data object: <itemizedlist>
                        <listitem>
                            <para> Registration </para>
                        </listitem>
                        <listitem>
                            <itemizedlist>
                                <listitem>
                                    <para> Name </para>
                                </listitem>
                                <listitem>
                                    <para> Affiliation </para>
                                </listitem>
                                <listitem>
                                    <para> Email address </para>
                                </listitem>
                                <listitem>
                                    <para> Full Contact Info </para>
                                </listitem>
                            </itemizedlist>
                        </listitem>
                        <listitem>
                            <para> Acceptance of the General Public Use Agreement or Restricted Data
                                Use Agreement, as applicable </para>
                        </listitem>
                        <listitem>
                            <para> A Statement of Intended Use that is compliant with the above
                                agreements. Such statements may be made submitted explicitly or made
                                implicitly via the data access portal interface. </para>
                        </listitem>
                    </itemizedlist>
                </para>
            </section>
            <section>
                <title>Conditions of Data Use</title>
                <para> The re-use of scientific data has the potential to greatly increase
                    communication, collaboration and synthesis within and among disciplines, and
                    thus is fostered, supported and encouraged. Permission to use this dataset is
                    granted to the Data User free of charge subject to the following terms: <itemizedlist>
                        <listitem>
                            <para> Acceptable Use. Use of the dataset will be restricted to
                                academic, research, educational, government, recreational, or other
                                not-for-profit professional purposes. The Data User is permitted to
                                produce and distribute derived works from this dataset provided that
                                they are released under the same license terms as those accompanying
                                this Data Set. Any other uses for the Data Set or its derived
                                products will require explicit permission from the dataset owner.
                            </para>
                        </listitem>
                        <listitem>
                            <para> Redistribution. The data are provided for use by the Data User.
                                The metadata and this license must accompany all copies made and be
                                available to all users of this Data Set. The Data User will not
                                redistribute the original Data Set beyond this collaboration sphere.
                            </para>
                        </listitem>
                        <listitem>
                            <para> Citation. It is considered a matter of professional ethics to
                                acknowledge the work of other scientists. Thus, the Data User will
                                properly cite the Data Set in any publications or in the metadata of
                                any derived data products that were produced using the Data Set.
                                Citation should take the following general form: Creator, Year of
                                Data Publication, Title of Dataset, Publisher, Dataset identifier.
                            </para>
                        </listitem>
                        <listitem>
                            <para> Acknowledgement. The Data User should acknowledge any
                                institutional support or specific funding awards referenced in the
                                metadata accompanying this dataset in any publications where the
                                Data Set contributed significantly to its content. Acknowledgements
                                should identify the supporting party, the party that received the
                                support, and any identifying information such as grant numbers.
                            </para>
                        </listitem>
                        <listitem>
                            <para> Notification. The Data User will notify the Data Set Contact when
                                any derivative work or publication based on or derived from the Data
                                Set is distributed. The Data User will provide the data contact with
                                two reprints of any publications resulting from use of the Data Set
                                and will provide copies, or on-line access to, any derived digital
                                products. Notification will include an explanation of how the Data
                                Set was used to produce the derived work. </para>
                        </listitem>
                        <listitem>
                            <para> Collaboration. The Data Set has been released in the spirit of
                                open scientific collaboration. Data Users are thus strongly
                                encouraged to consider consultation, collaboration and/or
                                co-authorship with the Data Set Creator. </para>
                        </listitem>
                    </itemizedlist> By accepting this Data Set, the Data User agrees to abide by the
                    terms of this agreement. The Data Owner shall have the right to terminate this
                    agreement immediately by written notice upon the Data User's breach of, or
                    non-compliance with, any of its terms. The Data User may be held responsible for
                    any misuse that is caused or encouraged by the Data User's failure to abide by
                    the terms of this agreement. </para>
            </section>
            <section>
                <title>Disclaimer</title>
                <para> While substantial efforts are made to ensure the accuracy of data and
                    documentation contained in this Data Set, complete accuracy of data and metadata
                    cannot be guaranteed. All data and metadata are made available "as is". The Data
                    User holds all parties involved in the production or distribution of the Data
                    Set harmless for damages resulting from its use or interpretation. </para>
            </section>
        </intellectualRights>
        <coverage>
            <geographicCoverage>
                <geographicDescription>North Inlet encompasses about 2,630 hectares of tidal marshes
                    and wetlands near Georgetown, South Carolina, USA. North Inlet-Winyah Bay
                    features high quality, ocean-dominated waters and salt marshes in North Inlet,
                    contrasting with the brackish waters and marshes of Winyah Bay. The bay estuary
                    is dominated by riverine discharges from a watershed impacted by agricultural,
                    municipal and industrial development. Former rice fields and canals provide
                    another system for study within the Reserve. The Debidue site is located at the
                    confluence of Town Creek and Debidue Creek. The Bread and Butter site is located
                    along the western shoreline of Town Creek adjacent to the mouth of Clambank
                    Creek. Oyster Landing in Crab Haul creek within the NORTH INLET ESTUARY SYSTEM
                    Georgetown, South Carolina. 33,20 lat. 79,11 long.</geographicDescription>
                <boundingCoordinates>
                    <westBoundingCoordinate>-79.2936</westBoundingCoordinate>
                    <eastBoundingCoordinate>-79.1042</eastBoundingCoordinate>
                    <northBoundingCoordinate>33.357</northBoundingCoordinate>
                    <southBoundingCoordinate>33.2125</southBoundingCoordinate>
                </boundingCoordinates>
            </geographicCoverage>
                <geographicCoverage>
                <geographicDescription>Oyster Landing in
                    Crab Haul Creek 33.21'2" Lat., 79.11'27" Long.</geographicDescription>
                <boundingCoordinates>
                    <westBoundingCoordinate>-79.1175</westBoundingCoordinate>
                    <eastBoundingCoordinate>-79.1175</eastBoundingCoordinate>
                    <northBoundingCoordinate>33.2106</northBoundingCoordinate>
                    <southBoundingCoordinate>33.2106</southBoundingCoordinate>
                </boundingCoordinates>
            </geographicCoverage>
            <temporalCoverage>
                <rangeOfDates>
                    <beginDate>
                        <calendarDate>1986-12-01</calendarDate>
                    </beginDate>
                    <endDate>
                        <calendarDate>1992-10-31</calendarDate>
                    </endDate>
                </rangeOfDates>
            </temporalCoverage>
        </coverage>
        <maintenance>
            <description>
                <section>
                    <title>Entry verification</title>
                    <para> Data are entered and edited on a weekly basis from the charts
                        collected from the weather shelter.  These data are entered into
                        an ascii data file and visually checked for errors.</para>
                </section>
                <section>
                    <title>Date of last update while at North Inlet LTER</title>
                    <para>October 31 1992</para>
                </section>
                <section>
                    <title>Last modification at LTER Network Office</title>
                    <para>Individual data files 
                        (LTER.NIN.NWS.1986.txt, LTER.NIN.NWS.1987.txt, LTER.NIN.NWS.1988.txt,
                        LTER.NIN.NWS.1989.txt, LTER.NIN.NWS.1990.txt, LTER.NIN.NWS.1991.txt,
                        LTER.NIN.NWS.1992.txt) were concatenated into a single file spanning the
                        dates from 1986 to 1992. Original fixed column format was changed to comma
                        separated value format and also inserted a header row for each type. 
                        These changes occured in March 2012</para>
                </section>
            </description>
        </maintenance>
        <contact>
            <positionName>Information Manager</positionName>
            <organizationName>LTER Network Office</organizationName>
            <address>
				<deliveryPoint>UNM Biology Department, MSC03-2020</deliveryPoint>
				<deliveryPoint>1 University of New Mexico</deliveryPoint>
				<city>Albuquerque</city>
				<administrativeArea>NM</administrativeArea>
				<postalCode>87131-0001</postalCode>
				<country>USA</country>
			</address>
            <phone phonetype="voice">505 277 2535</phone>
            <phone phonetype="fax">505 277 2541</phone>
            <electronicMailAddress>tech-support@lternet.edu</electronicMailAddress>
            <onlineUrl>http://www.lternet.edu</onlineUrl>
        </contact>
        <publisher>
            <organizationName>LTER Network Office</organizationName>
            <address>
				<deliveryPoint>UNM Biology Department, MSC03-2020</deliveryPoint>
				<deliveryPoint>1 University of New Mexico</deliveryPoint>
				<city>Albuquerque</city>
				<administrativeArea>NM</administrativeArea>
				<postalCode>87131-0001</postalCode>
				<country>USA</country>
			</address>
            <phone phonetype="voice">505 277 2535</phone>
            <phone phonetype="fax">505 277 2541</phone>
            <electronicMailAddress>tech-support@lternet.edu</electronicMailAddress>
            <onlineUrl>http://www.lternet.edu</onlineUrl>
        </publisher>
        <pubPlace>Long Term Ecological Research Network Office</pubPlace>
        <dataTable id="DailyWeatherParameter">
            <entityName>DailyWeatherParameter-NIN-LTER-1986-1992</entityName>
            <entityDescription>Daily Monitoring of Weather parameters for North Inlet Estuary, South Carolina, 
                from 1986 to 1992, North Inlet LTER</entityDescription>
            <physical>
                <objectName>LTER.NIN.NWS.csv</objectName>
                <size unit="byte">122(kb)</size>
                <dataFormat>
                    <textFormat>
                        <numHeaderLines>1</numHeaderLines>
                        <recordDelimiter>\r\n</recordDelimiter>
                        <physicalLineDelimiter>\r\n</physicalLineDelimiter>
                        <attributeOrientation>column</attributeOrientation>
                        <simpleDelimited>
                            <fieldDelimiter>,</fieldDelimiter>
                        </simpleDelimited>
                    </textFormat>
                </dataFormat>
                <distribution>
                    <online>
                        <url function="download">
                            http://nis.lternet.edu/NIN/data/LTER.NIN.NWS.csv</url>
                    </online>
                    <access authSystem="knb" order="allowFirst">
                        <allow>
                            <principal>uid=NIN,o=LTER,dc=ecoinformatics,dc=org</principal>
                            <permission>all</permission>
                        </allow>
                        <allow>
                            <principal>public</principal>
                            <permission>read</permission>
                        </allow>
                    </access>
                </distribution>
            </physical>
            <coverage>
                <geographicCoverage>
                    <geographicDescription>North Inlet encompasses about 2,630 hectares of tidal marshes
                        and wetlands near Georgetown, South Carolina, USA. North Inlet-Winyah Bay
                        features high quality, ocean-dominated waters and salt marshes in North Inlet,
                        contrasting with the brackish waters and marshes of Winyah Bay. The bay estuary
                        is dominated by riverine discharges from a watershed impacted by agricultural,
                        municipal and industrial development. Former rice fields and canals provide
                        another system for study within the Reserve. The Debidue site is located at the
                        confluence of Town Creek and Debidue Creek. The Bread and Butter site is located
                        along the western shoreline of Town Creek adjacent to the mouth of Clambank
                        Creek. Oyster Landing in Crab Haul creek within the NORTH INLET ESTUARY SYSTEM
                        Georgetown, South Carolina. 33,20 lat. 79,11 long.</geographicDescription>
                    <boundingCoordinates>
                        <westBoundingCoordinate>-79.2936</westBoundingCoordinate>
                        <eastBoundingCoordinate>-79.1042</eastBoundingCoordinate>
                        <northBoundingCoordinate>33.357</northBoundingCoordinate>
                        <southBoundingCoordinate>33.2125</southBoundingCoordinate>
                    </boundingCoordinates>
                </geographicCoverage>
                <geographicCoverage>
                    <geographicDescription>Oyster Landing in
                        Crab Haul Creek 33.21'2" Lat., 79.11'27" Long.</geographicDescription>
                    <boundingCoordinates>
                        <westBoundingCoordinate>-79.1175</westBoundingCoordinate>
                        <eastBoundingCoordinate>-79.1175</eastBoundingCoordinate>
                        <northBoundingCoordinate>33.2106</northBoundingCoordinate>
                        <southBoundingCoordinate>33.2106</southBoundingCoordinate>
                    </boundingCoordinates>
                </geographicCoverage>
                <temporalCoverage>
                    <rangeOfDates>
                        <beginDate>
                            <calendarDate>1986-12-01</calendarDate>
                        </beginDate>
                        <endDate>
                            <calendarDate>1992-10-31</calendarDate>
                        </endDate>
                    </rangeOfDates>
                </temporalCoverage>
            </coverage>
            <methods>
                <methodStep>
                    <description>
                        <section>
                            <title>Research methods</title>
                            <para> The NWS system in place at the Baruch Marine Laboratory was
                                purchased from the Qualimetrics Corporation of Sacramento CA.
                                Qualimetrics Inc. Box 230 Princeton, NJ. 08542 The system consists of
                                NWS approved: Instrument Shelter. Maximum and Minimum Thermometers
                                (Qualimetrics 4421), Hygrothermograph (Qualimetrics 5020) Barometer
                                (Qualimetrics 7010-A) Rain and snow gauge (Qualimetrics 6310).</para> 
                            <para>System Description</para>
                            <para>The system measures daily minimum, maximum and instantaneous
                                air temperature; daily rainfall, minimum and maximum relative humidity;
                                and minimum and maximum barometric pressure. Remote Site 1. Instrument
                                Shelter, standard U.S. Weather Bureau type. 2. Precipitation gauge, Dip
                                stick,(non recording) Standard U.S. Weather Bureau type. 3. Maximum and
                                Minimum Thermometers, Standard U.S. Weather Bureau type. 4. Hi-Q
                                Hygrothermograph. 5. Barometer (Qualimetrics).</para>
                            <para>System Description</para>
                            <para>The system is designed as follows. The instrument shelter is mounted onto a
                                concrete platform by bolts. This platform is located near the Oyster
                                landing Research site on Crab Haul Creek. The rain gauge is located
                                approximately 25 Feet from instrument shelter in a grass clearing. The
                                thermometers and hygrothermograph are located inside the instrument
                                shelter. The Barometer is located in the Data Management office.</para>
                            </section>
                        <section>
                            <para>Data collection</para>
                            <para>Data for these sensors are recorded on a chart every day at
                                1000 hr.  These daily data are brought into the lab once a
                                week and entered onto the computer.</para>
                        </section>
                        <section>
                            <title>Associated researchers and projects</title>
                            <para> Also see NIN01 (North Inlet Meteorological Data-Hourly Measurements).</para>
                        </section>
                        <section>
                            <title>Storage location and medium - A) Raw Data</title>
                            <para>The raw data are collected and recorded onto a form for air
                                temperatures and precipitation.  Relative Humidity and 
                                Barometric Pressure are recorded onto a seven day chart.
                            </para>
                        </section>
                        <section>
                            <title>Storage location and medium -  B) Edited Data </title>
                            <para> The raw data are perused for possible errors and then recorded
                                in an ASCII file, which is then edited for typographical
                                errors.  This file is then archived.</para>
                                               
                        </section>
                    </description>
                </methodStep>
                <methodStep>
                    <description>
                        <section>
                            <title>Experimental Design</title>
                            <para> Daily Monitoring of Weather parameters. </para>
                        </section>
                    </description>
                </methodStep>
            </methods>
            <attributeList>
                <attribute id="DailyWeatherParameter.Date">
                    <attributeName>Date</attributeName>
                    <attributeLabel>Date</attributeLabel>
                    <attributeDefinition>Day of month when sample collected</attributeDefinition>
                    <storageType>typeSystem="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-datatypes">Date</storageType>
                    <measurementScale>
                        <dateTime>
                            <formatString>YYYY-MM-DD</formatString>
                        </dateTime>
                    </measurementScale>
                </attribute>
                <attribute id="DailyWeatherParameter.Time">
                 <attributeName>Time</attributeName>
                 <attributeLabel>Time</attributeLabel>
                 <attributeDefinition> time when the sample was collected </attributeDefinition>
                    <storageType>typeSystem="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-datatypes">Time</storageType>
                    <measurementScale>
                        <dateTime>
                            <formatString>hh:mm:ss</formatString>
                        </dateTime>
                    </measurementScale>
                    <missingValueCode>
                        <code>-999</code>
                        <codeExplanation>missing value</codeExplanation>
                    </missingValueCode>
                </attribute>
                <attribute id="DailyWeatherParameter.Minimum_Air_Temp">
                    <attributeName>Minimum Air Temperature</attributeName>
                    <attributeLabel>Minimum_Air_Temp</attributeLabel>
                    <attributeDefinition>Minimum Air Temperature </attributeDefinition>
                    <measurementScale>
                        <interval>
                            <unit>
                                <standardUnit>celsius</standardUnit>
                            </unit>
                            <precision>0.1</precision>
                            <numericDomain>
                                <numberType>real</numberType>
                                <bounds>
                                    <minimum exclusive="false">-40.0 </minimum>
                                    <maximum exclusive="false">50</maximum>
                                </bounds>
                            </numericDomain>
                        </interval>
                    </measurementScale>
                    <missingValueCode>
                        <code>-99.9</code>
                        <codeExplanation>missing value</codeExplanation>
                    </missingValueCode>
                </attribute>
                <attribute id="DailyWeatherParameter.Current_Air_Temp">
                    <attributeName>Current Air Temperature</attributeName>
                    <attributeLabel>Current_Air_Temp</attributeLabel>
                    <attributeDefinition>Current Air Temperature</attributeDefinition>
                    <measurementScale>
                        <ratio>
                            <unit>
                                <standardUnit>celsius</standardUnit>
                            </unit>
                            <numericDomain>
                                <numberType>real</numberType>
                                <bounds>
                                    <minimum exclusive="false">-40.0</minimum>
                                    <maximum exclusive="false">50.0</maximum>
                                </bounds>
                            </numericDomain>
                        </ratio>
                    </measurementScale>
                    <missingValueCode>
                        <code>-99.9</code>
                        <codeExplanation>missing value</codeExplanation>
                    </missingValueCode>
                </attribute>
                <attribute id="DailyWeatherParameter.Maximum_Air_Temp">
                    <attributeName>Maximum Air Temperature</attributeName>
                    <attributeLabel>Maximum_Air_Temp</attributeLabel>
                    <attributeDefinition>Maximum Air Temperature</attributeDefinition>
                    <measurementScale>
                        <ratio>
                            <unit>
                                <standardUnit>celsius</standardUnit>
                            </unit>
                            <numericDomain>
                                <numberType>real</numberType>
                                <bounds>
                                    <minimum exclusive="false">-40.0</minimum>
                                    <maximum exclusive="false"> 50.0</maximum>
                                </bounds>
                            </numericDomain>
                        </ratio>
                    </measurementScale>
                    <missingValueCode>
                        <code>-99.9</code>
                        <codeExplanation>missing value</codeExplanation>
                    </missingValueCode>
                </attribute>
                <attribute id="DailyWeatherParameter.Precipitation">
                    <attributeName>Precipitation</attributeName>
                    <attributeLabel>Precipitation</attributeLabel>
                    <attributeDefinition>Precipitation</attributeDefinition>
                    <measurementScale>
                        <ratio>
                            <unit>
                                <standardUnit>millimeter</standardUnit>
                            </unit>
                            <precision>0.1</precision>
                            <numericDomain>
                                <numberType>real</numberType>
                                <bounds>
                                    <minimum exclusive="false"> 0 </minimum>
                                    <maximum exclusive="false"> 61.0</maximum>
                                </bounds>
                            </numericDomain>
                        </ratio>
                    </measurementScale>
                    <missingValueCode>
                        <code>-99.9</code>
                        <codeExplanation>missing value</codeExplanation>
                    </missingValueCode>
                </attribute>
                <attribute id="DailyWeatherParameter.Relative_Humidity_Minimum">
                    <attributeName>Relative Humidity Minimum</attributeName>
                    <attributeLabel>Relative_Humidity_Minimum</attributeLabel>
                    <attributeDefinition>Relative Humidity Minimum</attributeDefinition>
                    <measurementScale>
                        <ratio>
                            <unit>
                                <standardUnit>dimensionless</standardUnit>
                            </unit>
                            <precision>0.1</precision>
                            <numericDomain>
                                <numberType>real</numberType>
                                <bounds>
                                    <minimum exclusive="false"> 0 </minimum>
                                    <maximum exclusive="false"> 100</maximum>
                                </bounds>
                            </numericDomain>
                        </ratio>
                    </measurementScale>
                    <missingValueCode>
                        <code>-99.9</code>
                        <codeExplanation>missing value</codeExplanation>
                    </missingValueCode>
                </attribute>
                <attribute id="DailyWeatherParameter.Relative_Humidity_Maximum">
                    <attributeName>Relative Humidity Maximum</attributeName>
                    <attributeLabel>Relative_Humidity_Maximum</attributeLabel>
                    <attributeDefinition>Relative Humidity Maximum </attributeDefinition>
                    <measurementScale>
                        <ratio>
                            <unit>
                                <standardUnit>dimensionless</standardUnit>
                            </unit>
                            <precision>0.1</precision>
                            <numericDomain>
                                <numberType>real</numberType>
                                <bounds>
                                    <minimum exclusive="false"> 0 </minimum>
                                    <maximum exclusive="false"> 100</maximum>
                                </bounds>
                            </numericDomain>
                        </ratio>
                    </measurementScale>
                    <missingValueCode>
                        <code>-99.9</code>
                        <codeExplanation>missing value</codeExplanation>
                    </missingValueCode>
                </attribute>
                <attribute id="DailyWeatherParameter.Barometric_Pressure_Minimum">
                    <attributeName>Barometric Pressure Minimum</attributeName>
                    <attributeLabel>Barometric_Pressure_Minimum</attributeLabel>
                    <attributeDefinition>Barometric Pressure Minimum</attributeDefinition>
                    <measurementScale>
                        <ratio>
                            <unit>
                                <standardUnit>millibar</standardUnit>
                            </unit>
                            <precision>0.1</precision>
                            <numericDomain>
                                <numberType>real</numberType>
                                <bounds>
                                    <minimum exclusive="false"> 940 </minimum>
                                    <maximum exclusive="false"> 1040</maximum>
                                </bounds>
                            </numericDomain>
                        </ratio>
                    </measurementScale>
                    <missingValueCode>
                        <code>-99.9</code>
                        <codeExplanation>missing value</codeExplanation>
                    </missingValueCode>
                </attribute>
                <attribute id="DailyWeatherParameter.Barometric_Pressure_Maximum">
                    <attributeName>Barometric Pressure Maximum</attributeName>
                    <attributeLabel>Barometric_Pressure_Maximum</attributeLabel>
                    <attributeDefinition>Barometric Pressure Maximum</attributeDefinition>
                    <measurementScale>
                        <ratio>
                            <unit>
                                <standardUnit>millibar</standardUnit>
                            </unit>
                            <precision>0.1</precision>
                            <numericDomain>
                                <numberType>real</numberType>
                                <bounds>
                                    <minimum exclusive="false"> 940 </minimum>
                                    <maximum exclusive="false"> 1040</maximum>
                                </bounds>
                            </numericDomain>
                        </ratio>
                    </measurementScale>
                    <missingValueCode>
                        <code>-99.9</code>
                        <codeExplanation>missing value</codeExplanation>
                    </missingValueCode>
                </attribute>   
            </attributeList>
            <numberOfRecords>2162</numberOfRecords>
        </dataTable>
    </dataset>
    
</eml:eml>
